{
    "id": "c041ef7d04b241589007a0bf26eca442",
    "title": "Used To And Be Used To",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I am not used to ............................. late hours.",
            "description": "The to in be used to is a preposition. We use ing forms after prepositions. ",
            "answers": [
                "work",
                "working",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "046327d684a946fa90fa8677985f5d6f"
        },
        {
            "question": "He used to ............................. a lot.",
            "description": "We use an infinitive after used to.",
            "answers": [
                "smoke",
                "smoking",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fd28373b08b545208f01837e8d8bddf9"
        },
        {
            "question": "I used to ………………………… pop music, but now I don’t.",
            "description": "We use an infinitive after used to.",
            "answers": [
                "hate",
                "hating",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "59b0e0e32a5e43e6808593f1793718a0"
        },
        {
            "question": "When we were children, we used to ………………………… a lot of time playing hide and seek.",
            "description": "We use an infinitive after used to.",
            "answers": [
                "spend",
                "spending"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ebe94e8a67924442bb65c64a41940558"
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………………… be afraid of spiders.",
            "description": "We use used to to talk about things that happened at an earlier stage of our life.",
            "answers": [
                "used to",
                "am used to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "674c662dbcab4957aff644280cd363d1"
        },
        {
            "question": "You used not to eat meat, ………………………….?",
            "description": "Used is not used in questions tags. Instead we use did.",
            "answers": [
                "used you",
                "didn't you",
                "did you"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "57ae88d1c23f4da3b9d64949cae241a3"
        },
        {
            "question": "When I was in Mumbai, I ………………………….. visit my grandparents every month.",
            "description": "We use used to to talk about things that happened at an earlier stage of our life.",
            "answers": [
                "used to",
                "was used to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2ade3bce21c5473e9f198c515ff7a94f"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………………… my grandparents twice last month.",
            "description": "We do not use used to to simply say how many times something happened.",
            "answers": [
                "visited",
                "used to visit",
                "was used to visiting"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "af9bf30e19394638855bcb7a1490732c"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ……………………………….  a big car, but now I do.",
            "description": "We use didn’t use to to talk about something we hadn’t done in the past.",
            "answers": [
                "didn't use to drive",
                "wasn't used to driving"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2db682bef10b49d2ad5eaf02535f5d89"
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………………………… a big car so I was scared.",
            "description": "If you aren’t used to doing something, it is not familiar to you.",
            "answers": [
                "didn't use to drive",
                "wasn't used to driving"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "87731a699eb14495afd6f6ffc266e3de"
        },
        {
            "question": "It took me quite some time to get used to ………………………….. in a big city.",
            "description": "We use an ing form after get used to.",
            "answers": [
                "live",
                "living"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "05c7164e7576445eac3ee3d3380be1e5"
        },
        {
            "question": "Little by little, she …………………………….. her new family.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "used to",
                "became used to",
                "got used to"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "fb5445a87da640ea945cb5ccd549e6f2"
        }
    ]
}